export const QUIZZ_DATA = [
  {
    topic: 'World Literature',
    isActive: true,
    id: 'l1',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: 'lq1',
        question:
          "What was the name of the king who was the main character of William Shakespeare's tragedy 'Hamlet'?",
        options: ['Richard', 'Hamlet', 'Henry'],
        answer: 'Hamlet',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq2',
        question:
          'Which book by J. R. R. Tolkien tells about the adventures of a hobbit named Frodo Baggins?',
        options: [
          "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone",
          'The Lord of the Rings',
          'War and Peace',
        ],
        answer: 'The Lord of the Rings',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq3',
        question:
          "Which play by William Shakespeare begins with the lines 'As you likeit'?",
        options: ['Romeo and Juliet', 'How do you like it', 'Othello'],
        answer: 'How do you like it',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq4',
        question:
          "Who wrote the novel 'Monday Begins on Saturday' about humorous adventures in a fantastic institute?",
        options: [
          'George Orwell',
          'Arkady and Boris Strugatsky',
          'Jane Austen',
        ],
        answer: 'Arkady and Boris Strugatsky',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq5',
        question: 'What pseudonym did the English writer Samuel Clemens use?',
        options: ['Mark Twain', 'George Orwell', 'Charles Dickens'],
        answer: 'Mark Twain',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq6',
        question:
          "Which book by George Orwell describes a totalitarian society where the government controls every aspect of the citizens' lives?",
        options: ['1984', 'Fahrenheit 451', 'Matrix'],
        answer: '1984',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq7',
        question:
          "Who wrote the comedy 'Don Juan' about the legendary seducer and social rebel?",
        options: ['William Shakespeare', 'Moliere', 'Oscar Wilde'],
        answer: 'Moliere',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq8',
        question:
          'Which writer created a character named Jane Eyre, who became the main character of the novel of the same name?',
        options: ['Emily Brontë', 'Jane Austen', 'Charlotte Brontë'],
        answer: 'Charlotte Brontë',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq9',
        question:
          "Who wrote the comedy play 'Pinocchio', about the adventures of a wooden puppet boy?",
        options: [
          'Hans Christian Andersen',
          'Carlo Collodi',
          'Astrid Lindgren',
        ],
        answer: 'Carlo Collodi',
      },
      {
        id: 'lq10',
        question:
          'Which book by Oscar Wilde tells about the adventures of a young gentleman who sold his soul for eternal youth?',
        options: [
          'Portrait of Dorian Gray',
          'Pride and Prejudice',
          'War of the Worlds',
        ],
        answer: 'Portrait of Dorian Gray',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: 'Literary masterpieces',
    isActive: false,
    id: 'l2',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: 'la1',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Master and Margarita", which combines satire, fantasy and philosophy?',
        options: ['Fyodor Dostoevsky', 'Mikhail Bulgakov', 'Leo Tolstoy'],
        answer: 'Mikhail Bulgakov',
      },
      {
        id: 'la2',
        question:
          'Which book by James Joyce is considered one of the most difficult to read because of its experimental style?',
        options: ['Ulysses', "Finnegan's Wake", 'Arch'],
        answer: 'Ulysses',
      },
      {
        id: 'la3',
        question:
          'Who wrote the fairy tale "Alice in Wonderland", which became a classic of children\'s literature?',
        options: ['Jonathan Swift', 'Lewis Carroll', 'Roger Hobbs'],
        answer: 'Lewis Carroll',
      },
      {
        id: 'la4',
        question:
          'Which writer created a series of books about a young wizard named Harry Potter?',
        options: ['J. R. R. Tolkien', 'George RR Martin', 'JK Rowling'],
        answer: 'JK Rowling',
      },
      {
        id: 'la5',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Great Gatsby", which is considered one of the best American works of the 20th century?',
        options: [
          'Ernest Hemingway',
          'Francis Scott Fitzgerald',
          'John Steinbeck',
        ],
        answer: 'Francis Scott Fitzgerald',
      },
      {
        id: 'la6',
        question:
          'Which book by Mark Twain tells about the adventures of the boy Tom Sawyer on the banks of the Mississippi River?',
        options: [
          'The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn',
          'The Adventures of Oliver Twist',
          'The Adventures of Ali Baba and the Forty Thieves',
        ],
        answer: 'The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn',
      },
      {
        id: 'la7',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Cherry Orchard", which describes the fate of a noble family facing financial problems?',
        options: ['Anton Chekhov', 'Fyodor Dostoevsky', 'Ivan Turgenev'],
        answer: 'Anton Chekhov',
      },
      {
        id: 'la8',
        question:
          'Which writer created a character named Sherlock Holmes, solving complex criminal cases?',
        options: ['Agatha Christie', 'Arthur Conan Doyle', 'Raymond Chandler'],
        answer: 'Arthur Conan Doyle',
      },
      {
        id: 'la9',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Dictator\'s Workshop", which tells the story of a tyrant who decided to become a writer?',
        options: ['George Orwell', 'Albert Camus', 'Miguel de Cervantes'],
        answer: 'Miguel de Cervantes',
      },
      {
        id: 'la10',
        question:
          'Which book by John Steinbeck describes the life of poor metalworkers during the Great Depression in the United States?',
        options: ['Gump the Mouse', 'Grapes of Wrath', 'Quiet Don'],
        answer: 'Grapes of Wrath',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: 'Great novels',
    isActive: false,
    id: 'l3',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: 'lw1',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "1984", which describes a totalitarian world where every step of a person is controlled by the government?',
        options: ['George Orwell', 'Ernest Hemingway', 'Franz Kafka'],
        answer: 'George Orwell',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw2',
        question:
          'Which writer created a series of books about the adventures of Robin Hood and his merry company?',
        options: ['William Shakespeare', 'Walter Scott', 'Howard Pyle'],
        answer: 'Walter Scott',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw3',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "War and Peace", which describes the events during the Napoleonic Wars?',
        options: ['Leo Tolstoy', 'Alexander Dumas', 'Fyodor Dostoevsky'],
        answer: 'Leo Tolstoy',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw4',
        question:
          'Which book by Jane Austen is about love and social conventions in 19th century English society?',
        options: ['Pride and Prejudice', 'Emma', 'Mind and feeling'],
        answer: 'Pride and Prejudice',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw5',
        question: 'Who wrote the novel "Little Women"?',
        options: ['Louise May Olcott', 'Jane Austen', 'Emily Brontë'],
        answer: 'Louise May Olcott',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw6',
        question:
          'Which book by Mark Twain tells about the adventures of the main character in a kayak on the Mississippi River?',
        options: [
          'The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn',
          'The Adventures of Tom Sawyer',
          'The Adventures of Don Quixote',
        ],
        answer: 'The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw7',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Dictator\'s Workshop", which tells the story of a tyrant who decided to become a writer?',
        options: ['George Orwell', 'Albert Camus', 'Miguel de Cervantes'],
        answer: 'Miguel de Cervantes',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw8',
        question:
          'Which book by John Steinbeck describes the life of poor metalworkers during the Great Depression in the United States?',
        options: ['Gump the Mouse', 'Grapes of Wrath', 'Quiet Don'],
        answer: 'Grapes of Wrath',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw9',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "A Thousand Wonderful Sonnets", which is considered one of the greatest works of world literature?',
        options: [
          'William Shakespeare',
          'Dante Alighieri',
          'Francois Rabelais',
        ],
        answer: 'Dante Alighieri',
      },
      {
        id: 'lw10',
        question:
          'Which writer created a character named Sherlock Holmes, solving complex criminal cases?',
        options: ['Agatha Christie', 'Arthur Conan Doyle', 'Raymond Chandler'],
        answer: 'Arthur Conan Doyle',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: 'Literary legends',
    isActive: false,
    id: 'l4',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: 'lr1',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Great Gatsby", which is considered one of the best American works of the 20th century?',
        options: [
          'Ernest Hemingway',
          'Francis Scott Fitzgerald',
          'John Steinbeck',
        ],
        answer: 'Francis Scott Fitzgerald',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr2',
        question:
          'Which book by Mark Twain tells about the adventures of the boy Tom Sawyer on the banks of the Mississippi River?',
        options: [
          'The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn',
          'The Adventures of Oliver Twist',
          'The Adventures of Ali Baba and the Forty Thieves',
        ],
        answer: 'The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr3',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Cherry Orchard", which describes the fate of a noble family facing financial problems?',
        options: ['Anton Chekhov', 'Fyodor Dostoevsky', 'Ivan Turgenev'],
        answer: 'Anton Chekhov',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr4',
        question:
          'Which writer created a character named Sherlock Holmes, solving complex criminal cases?',
        options: ['Agatha Christie', 'Arthur Conan Doyle', 'Raymond Chandler'],
        answer: 'Arthur Conan Doyle',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr5',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "A Thousand Wonderful Sonnets", which is considered one of the greatest works of world literature?',
        options: [
          'William Shakespeare',
          'Dante Alighieri',
          'Francois Rabelais',
        ],
        answer: 'Dante Alighieri',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr6',
        question:
          'Which book by John Steinbeck describes the life of poor metalworkers during the Great Depression in the United States?',
        options: ['Gump the Mouse', 'Grapes of Wrath', 'Quiet Don'],
        answer: 'Grapes of Wrath',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr7',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "1984", which describes a totalitarian world where every step of a person is controlled by the government?',
        options: ['George Orwell', 'Ernest Hemingway', 'Franz Kafka'],
        answer: 'George Orwell',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr8',
        question:
          'Which writer created a series of books about the adventures of Robin Hood and his merry company?',
        options: ['William Shakespeare', 'Walter Scott', 'Howard Pyle'],
        answer: 'Walter Scott',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr9',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "War and Peace", which describes the events during the Napoleonic Wars?',
        options: ['Leo Tolstoy', 'Alexander Dumas', 'Fyodor Dostoevsky'],
        answer: 'Leo Tolstoy',
      },
      {
        id: 'lr10',
        question:
          'Which book by Jane Austen is about love and social conventions in 19th century English society?',
        options: ['Pride and Prejudice', 'Emma', 'Mind and feeling'],
        answer: 'Pride and Prejudice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: 'Cult works',
    isActive: false,
    id: 'l5',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: 'ls1',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Master and Margarita", which combines satire, fantasy and philosophy?',
        options: ['Fyodor Dostoevsky', 'Mikhail Bulgakov', 'Leo Tolstoy'],
        answer: 'Mikhail Bulgakov',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls2',
        question:
          'Which book by James Joyce is considered one of the most difficult to read because of its experimental style?',
        options: ['Ulysses', "Finnegan's Wake", 'Arch'],
        answer: 'Ulysses',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls3',
        question:
          'Who wrote the fairy tale "Alice in Wonderland", which became a classic of children\'s literature?',
        options: ['Jonathan Swift', 'Lewis Carroll', 'Roger Hobbs'],
        answer: 'Lewis Carroll',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls4',
        question:
          'Which writer created a series of books about a young wizard named Harry Potter?',
        options: ['J. R. R. Tolkien', 'George RR Martin', 'JK Rowling'],
        answer: 'JK Rowling',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls5',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Great Gatsby", which is considered one of the best American works of the 20th century?',
        options: [
          'Ernest Hemingway',
          'Francis Scott Fitzgerald',
          'John Steinbeck',
        ],
        answer: 'Francis Scott Fitzgerald',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls6',
        question:
          'Which book by Mark Twain tells about the adventures of the boy Tom Sawyer on the banks of the Mississippi River?',
        options: [
          'The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn',
          'The Adventures of Oliver Twist',
          'The Adventures of Ali Baba and the Forty Thieves',
        ],
        answer: 'The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls7',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Cherry Orchard", which describes the fate of a noble family facing financial problems?',
        options: ['Anton Chekhov', 'Fyodor Dostoevsky', 'Ivan Turgenev'],
        answer: 'Anton Chekhov',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls8',
        question:
          'Which writer created a character named Sherlock Holmes, solving complex criminal cases?',
        options: ['Agatha Christie', 'Arthur Conan Doyle', 'Raymond Chandler'],
        answer: 'Arthur Conan Doyle',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls9',
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Dictator\'s Workshop", which tells the story of a tyrant who decided to become a writer?',
        options: ['George Orwell', 'Albert Camus', 'Miguel de Cervantes'],
        answer: 'Miguel de Cervantes',
      },
      {
        id: 'ls10',
        question:
          'Which book by John Steinbeck describes the life of poor metalworkers during the Great Depression in the United States?',
        options: ['Gump the Mouse', 'Grapes of Wrath', 'Quiet Don'],
        answer: 'Grapes of Wrath',
      },
    ],
  },
];
